Romulo Leitao

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER



Phone Number (819) 943-5057

Email Address romulojleitao@gmail.com

LinkedIn Romulo Leitao

GitHub romuloleitao

SKILLS

.Net Core **Angular** Intermediate Intermediate HTMI 5 CSS3 Advanced Advanced C# JavaScript | Intermediate **TypeScript** Advanced SOL Server **Entity** Intermediate Framework Intermediate **Jasmine NUnit** Intermediate Intermediate Agile Git

Advanced

Advanced

RESUME

Software developer with experience in coding, testing and continuous improvement of features, in addition to relevant experience in the administrative area. 3 years of experience in Front-End and Back-End development using technologies such as .Net Core and Angular JS. Bachelor of Business Administration and several specialization courses in the technology area. Committed and focused on achieving the company's goals and always motivated to learn new technologies.

WORK EXPERIENCE

CGI Inc.

Software Developer

(September 2019 - May 2020)

Development of functionalities to create, read, modify and delete data for many screens in a Windows Forms Desktop application. Creation of batch scripts for perform services. Technology: .NET Windows Forms, C#.

Omniscient Technology

Software Developer

(August 2017 - September 2019)

Development of a web application with Angular and .Net Core. Use of PostMan to test the requisitions from database and then use the data in the interface created with Angular 2+. Project with agile methodology - SCRUM. Technology: C#, Typescript, .NET Core, Angular, NUnit, Jasmine, Protractor, Entity, SQL Server.

Creation of functionalities for a PWA. Mobile web system used for customer visit services, calculating invoices, showing tracking, taking signatures, etc. Realized with Aurelia technology in Front-End and .NET Core for the WEB API and with a well-established structure of agile methodology - Scrum. Technology: C#, Typescript, .NET Core, Aurelia, NUnit, Jasmine, Entity, SQL Server.

Ceará Water and Sewage Company - Cagece

(December 2013 - May 2017)

Administrative Analyst - Process Auditor

Study of administrative processes in all areas of the company to check that the rules, regulations and legislation are being followed. Creation of a report with the results.

EDUCATION

Federal University of Ceara

Bachelor's Degree Business Administration

(February 2005 - June 2010)

Estácio de Sá University

Analysis and Systems Development Information Technology

(June 2014 - June 2015)

LANGUAGES

French English

Fluent Fluent

Portuguese

Native